Entonces realmente piensas
your grandma will
come out of the coma
if she sees her daughter?
I mean, your mom.
Well, I’ve read about
some cases like this.
People in comas,
they can feel everything.
Really?
Yeah.
What that guy doing here?
Who is he?
Oh, god.
Let's go.
Miss Rose, wait.
Mister Henderson would
like to speak with you.
He has my phone number.
He can call.
Why bother when we
can talk face to face?
Do you have any updates
about my mother?
Don't worry.
My best people are on it.
We'll get the results.
Fine.
When you have the results,
text me.
Bye.
Gina, I looked at your schedule
for the week and realized
you're working too much.
Did you go through my calendar?
Oh my gosh.
You're like James Bond,
if he were a creepy stalker.
I did it to free you
from all obligations.
Nice.
Me too?
Walt,
quit with your spy things.
My father needs to be convinced
this relationship isn't fake.
So now you're getting
my full dossier.
Everything's here.
My habits.
Where I like to vacation,
my favorite foods,
preferred whiskey.
How boring.
It also...
has my sexual
preferences.